hello, once again you are very
welcome to our YouTube channel, today we
will do a comparison between two health insurance companies, the
help companies of our house, ICICI
Bank and ICICI Lombard,
please watch this video till the end
because in this video you will
get information regarding health insurance which will be very useful for you in your life
and those who are
against health insurance or are already
associated with health insurance, they
can contact us through this channel
and get information, so let's start the
video, first of all let us know the difference in these insurance
because this thing sets these plans
apart from each other, first of all we will
talk about these rich options, in the help
insurance plan you get
these oil constipation options from three lakhs to one crore rupees
and in the ICICI Lombard I have
plan you get news options from only one lakh to 10 years,
now road ambulance, if you have comments, in the
help companies you get ₹3000
and in the help insurance plan I will give you  Let us
cover road end charges up to ₹15 and
you get winter, which is in comparison,
you get this mixture and virus plus
animal, you are covered only up to 50 thousand, that too
a limit has been mentioned here, you
only get organ donor expenses of two addresses
are covered here, now let's talk about no
claim bonus, friends, in Max Bupa Health
Complaint you get 1g Guys, 20 per cent of this
mins that every free home, which
goes up to a maximum of 100 percent, bonus
marks never get reduced in Fufa,
plain emerging women helpline app
gets the benefit of chocolate boys, additional
same top ten percent in every sphere, only
volume goes up to a maximum of 50 percent
and Disturb Artist, here this bonus is
relative, you get 100 per cent in the case
of sleep on
spinks,
which you get on benefits in Have Complaint, from ₹1000 per
day  ₹4000 code and come on every Plus,
while doing this we told you there
is news of ₹500 on root options and for three, four or five nights
you get ₹1000 on introductions like this and along with that
you get up to
₹2000 hospital gas available at the office except near the last, we
Max Bupa Health companies get hair checkup on
Thursday and in this plant you
get free health check-up, every
politician friends, we have talked about the
difference between these plants, now we will
talk about these plants, after this there is
tank demand, till pain infection
treatment plant, so systems are
subscribed to both of these in which
for subscription and
week addition you get treatment for four days, now
let's talk about treatment, if you have done it on the other
side then comment in the comment box below, then you get
system in life from which you get
15 days and you
get decision on cancellation, now we will talk about
those subscriptions, you do not get any,
subscribe from here to ₹10  Talking
about the benefits which are available in the market but
cannot be subscribed,
I get
Animals like charges
from Haridwar to Rs.7000. Now we will talk about
those benefits which you do
not get only I Aslam. You get maternity benefit
after 3 years of meeting, there are
some limits in it that you will get Rs. 2 lakhs. For
normal delivery you get cover of
Rs.10,000 and above and Cerebral benefits for you are covered for
Rs.15000. In plan of 3500, normal
delivery you get clothes for Rs.15000 and Cesarean
you are covered for Rs.25000 and for
normal delivery for 10 years you get clothes for
Rs.25000. Well clothes for Rs.50.
You also get post natal expenses of Rs.2000
if it is a human baby, you get covered
with Rs.10000 limit. You get the
benefits of wellness and preventive health care
which is Rs.2 lakhs.  In the plan of Rs.
2500 you get Rs. 2500 and in the plan of 3, 4, 5 lakh
you get Rs. 5000 and
in the policy of 10 years from 12 months to 10 years you get
limited benefits from Tata Sons. In the beginning of 10 years you get some
option of alarm cover like
you get critical illness cover
and maximum for 2010
in three to ten years plan you will understand hundred percent of
quality. Who will understand lip benefit. You
get Rs. 10 for day one pinch policy. If
you have taken some policy, you will get helpline for some complaints.
You will get Rs. 20000
free treatment for kidney disease. If you
use 4G for 2 to 5 lakh minutes and in the beginning of 4 to 10 years
you do not get any complaints within this year,
you have been given some value added
services also. You get free health
check-up.
You get maximum two options. You get access to medical
practitioners like
you can chat online.
You get the facility of specialty consultation,
you also get the facility of Diet and Vitamin A consultation here, now we will talk
about the waiting ticket of these countries
which is approximately 100% in humans, the
initial waiting period is 15 months and
for specific diseases you have a
waiting period of 24 months, please
for West Indies you have a waiting period of 36 months with Max Bupa Welcome
Parents Lal Mirch and
in I Aslam you have a waiting period of 48 months with this
and for maternity benefit daily you have a
waiting period of 36 months with ICICI
Lombard, friends this was a little
information about Max Bupa Welcome
Parents Comparison,
please tell me through comments how
you liked this video, if you have any doubt or question
related to this video then
ask me in the comments, if you found this video really
useful then you must share this video
with your relatives on WhatsApp, it will
help them and you will get thanks, do
n't forget to subscribe to my channel  Please
like the video so that my
motivation remains the same and I have
brought such informative videos for you.
Press the bell icon so that
you get the first updates regarding my latest videos.
Thank you for watching my
video
[Music]